(Bert:)I bet if we put
our heads together,
(Bert:)we could come up
with a solution.
(Sheldon:)We... Hang on.
(Sheldon:)You're my enemy.
(Sheldon:)Now, the enemy of the enemy
is my friend.
(Sheldon:)And right now,
I'm my own worst enemy.
(Sheldon:)That makes you my fr--
Okay, I'm good to go.
(Leonard:)Great.
(Bert:)Now that we're friends,
want to see if we can
(Bert:)get tickets
to a taping of Ellen?
(Sheldon:)You know what?
This isn't gonna work.
(Bert:)Sheldon... wait.
(Bert:)You know, you've got
a lot to be happy about.
(Bert:)You're at the top
of your field,
(Bert:)you have a great girlfriend.
Yes! That's right!
I have Amy!
(Sheldon:)In the past, you've
professed feelings for her.
(Sheldon:)Does it eat you up inside
(Sheldon:)that I have her
and you don't?
(Bert:)It used to.
(Bert:)But now that I'm rich
and successful,
(Bert:)I think I can do better.
(Sheldon:)I can't believe
you punched Bert.